Seymour S. Cohen Papers 1938-1990 Mss.Ms.Coll.48
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1940-1990; 11.5 linear feet
  - Chargaff, Erwin, 1942-1989; 72.0 Item(s) (Box 5)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia -- Chargaff, Erwin; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Charles-Leopold Mayer Prize; Honors -- Nobel Prize; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Publication; Recommendations; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Chemical and Engineering News, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Chen, Chung-Tai Jack, 1978-1983 (Box 5)
  - Chen, Kuang Yu, 1986, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cheng, Yung-Chi (Tommy), 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Chiba University, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Ch'ien, Lawrence T., 1971 (Box 5)
  - The Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, 1945-1973 (Box 5)
  - Chou, David Ting-Chao, 1975-1984 (Box 5)
  - The Ciba Foundation, 1955, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - The City College, 1976-1990 (Box 5)
  - The City University of New York, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Clark, Betsy, [1968] (Box 5)
  - Clark, Eloise E., 1963-1983 (Box 5)
  - Clark, Jeffrey L., 1976 (Box 5)
    Levin, Eugene G.
  - Clark, Joseph S., 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Clarke, Hans T., 1945 (Box 5)
  - Claude, Albert, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Cline, Richard E., 1958 (Box 5)
    Green, Maurice
  - Cluff, Leighton E., 1979 (Box 5)
  - Cocito, Carlo G., 1971-1984 (Box 5)
    -See also Ser.I, Université Catholique de Louvain
  - Cohen, D. Walter, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Georges N., 1986, [198-] (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Philip P., 1963 (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Sasson, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Stanley, 1974-1983 (Box 6)
  - Cohn, Melvin, 1950-1951 (Box 6)
  - Cohn, Mildred, 1962-1974 (Box 6)
  - Cohn, Waldo E., 1950-1970 (Box 6)
    -See also Ser.I, Progress in Nucleic Acid Research and Molecular Biology
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Collège de France, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
    Jacob, François
  - The College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Coller, Barry S., 1986 (Box 6)
  - Colorado Regional Cancer Center, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Colowick, Sidney P., 1972, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Columbia University, 1940-1976 (Box 6)
    Chargaff, Erwin; Hayashi, Teru
  - Columbia University Press, 1966-1984 (Box 6)
  - Coman, Dale Rex, 1972, 1987, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Committee on Space Research, 1962 (Box 6)
  - The Commonwealth Fund (Box 6)
    - Folder #1, 1948-1956 (Box 6)
    - Folder #2, 1957-1986 (Box 6)
  - Congdon, C.C., 1971 (Box 6)
  - Connecticut. Department of Higher Education, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Cournand, André, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Courtois, Jean Émile (Box 6)
    -See Ser.I, Société de Chimie Biologique
  - Cox, David J., 1959-1962 (Box 6)
  - Cox, Edward C., 1965 (Box 6)
  - Cowan, Ruth S., 1984 (Box 6)
  - Coward, James K., 1976 (Box 6)
  - Cox, David, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Cozzarelli, Nicholas R., 1976 (Box 6)
  - Creighton University, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Cuatrecasas, Pedro, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
  - Cummings, Donald J., 1964-1972 (Box 6)
  - Current Contents, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Current Topics in Developmental Biology, 1965-1970 (Box 6)
    Monroy, Alberto; Moscona, A.A.
  - Cyclo Chemical Corporation, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Dales, Samuel, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Daniels, Farrington, Jr., 1963 (Box 6)
  - Darby, William J., 1977 (Box 6)
  - Darnell, James, Jr., 1962, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Daves, G. Doyle, Jr., 1981 (Box 6)
  - Davidson, J.N., 1954 (Box 6)
  - Davidson, Norman, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Davis, Alan C., 1977 (Box 6)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1950-1986, n.d. (Box 6)
    Neyman, Jerzy
  - Davis, Rowland H., 1973, 1980 (Box 6)
  - The Lady Davis Fellowship Trust, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Dearborn, Dorr G., 1978 (Box 6)
  - De Clercq, Erik, 1977-1979 (Box 6)
  - De Courcy, Samuel J., Jr., 1969 (Box 6)
  - De Hevesy, George Charles, 1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Marcel Dekker, Inc., 1979 (Box 6)
  - Delbrück, Max, 1946-1975; 24.0 Item(s) (Box 6)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Ethical issues; Honors -- National Medal of Science; Luria, Salvador Edward; Olby, Robert Cecil
  - Delihas, Nicholas, 1960-1986 (Box 6)
  - Delk, Ann, 1969 (Box 6)
  - DeMars, Robert, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Demerec, M[ilislav], 1952 (Box 7)
  - de Robichon-Dzylmajster, Huguette, 1968-1974 (Box 7)
  - Deutscher, Murray P., 1976 (Box 7)
  - Dickens, F., 1951, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Dietz, David, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Di Mayorca, Giampiero, 1969-1977 (Box 7)
  - Dindal, Daniel L., 1982 (Box 7)
  - Dion, Arnold S., 1966-1981 (Box 7)
  - Dische, Zacharias, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Dobrynin, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Doering, Alice McGovern, 1965, n.d. (Box 7)
  - Doermann, A.H., 1947-1951 (Box 7)
  - Dominion Rubber Company Limited, 1947 (Box 7)
  - Donachie, W.D., 1971 (Box 7)
  - Dorfman, Albert, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Doty, Paul, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Doudoroff, Michael, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Drabkin, David L., 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Drach, John C., 1979 (Box 7)
  - Dratman, Mary, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Drug Research Reports, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Duckworth, Donna H., 1969 (Box 7)
  - Dudock, Bernard, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Dunn, Arnold, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Duschinsky, Robert, 1959-1970 (Box 7)
  - Eakin, Robert E., 1962 (Box 7)
  - Earhart, Charles F., 1969 (Box 7)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1947 (Box 7)
  - Eberhart, Bruce, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Ebringer, Libor, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Edelstein, Sidney, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Edizioni Scientifiche e Tecniche, 1976, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Edsall, John, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Edwards, Joshua L., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Egami, Fujio, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1956-1962 (Box 7)
  - Eisen, Herman N., 1988 (Box 7)
  - Elderfield, Robert C., 1972 (Box 7)
  - Eliel, Ernest L., 1982 (Box 7)
  - Elson, David, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Elson, Elliot, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Enders, John F., 1963 (Box 7)
  - Engel, Lewis L., 1971 (Box 7)
  - Engelhardt, Edward L., 1968 (Box 7)
  - Ennis, Herbert Leo, 1968-1982 (Box 7)
  - Ephrati-Elizur, E., 1969 (Box 7)
  - Epstein, Herman T., 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Errera, Maurice, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Evans, Earl A., Jr., 1968-1983 (Box 7)
  - Ezekiel, David H., 1967, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Fair, William R., 1970 (Box 7)
  - Fairley, James L., 1957 (Box 7)
  - Falkner, Frank, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Farber, Sidney, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Farkas, G.L., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Favre, Alain, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Fedele, Louis A., 1981 (Box 7)
  - Feder, Ned (Box 7)
    -See Ser.I, Stewart, Walter W.
  - Feinstein, Otto, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Feltham, L.A.W., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Ferguson, James, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Fiers, Walter, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Fine, Miriam, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Fink, Robert M., 1960 (Box 7)
  - Fischer, Glenn A., 1966 (Box 7)
    Chu, M.Y.
  - Fisher, Waldo R., 1970 (Box 7)
  - Flaks, Joel G., 1960 (Box 7)
  - Flesch, Peter, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher, Edward A., 1972 (Box 7)
  - Fletcher, Hewitt G., Jr., 1963-1968 (Box 7)
  - Flores-Merino, Hector E., 1980-1982 (Box 7)
  - The Florida State University, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Florkin, Marcel, 1962-1963 (Box 7)
    -See also Ser.I, International Union of Biochemistry
  - Flynn, Richard John, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Folk, J.E., 1981 (Box 7)
  - The Food and Drug Law Institute, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Forbes, Martin, 1964-1968 (Box 7)
  - Foss, John G., 1973 (Box 7)
  - Fox, Jack J., 1958-1986 (Box 7)
  - Fox, Sidney W., 1966 (Box 7)
  - Fraenkel, D.G., 1967, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Fraley, Pierre, 1961 (Box 7)
  - François, Jacob (Box 7)
    -See Ser.I, Institut Pasteur
  - Frank, Arlen W., 1984 (Box 7)
  - Franklin, Richard M., 1968 (Box 7)
  - Fraser, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Freda, Celia (Box 7)
    -See Ser.I, Prairie, Celia Esther Freda
  - Fredrick, Jerome F., 1979 (Box 7)
  - Freireich, Emil J., 1974 (Box 7)
  - Fresco, Jacques R., 1962, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Fridovich, Irwin, 1972, 1979, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Friedkin, Morris, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Friend, Charlotte, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Fruton, Joseph S., 1947-1982 (Box 7)
  - Fujiwara, M., 1963 (Box 8)
  - Fukuma, Isamu, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Furie, Barbara (Box 8)
    -See Ser.I, Furie, Bruce
  - Furie, Bruce, 1990 (Box 8)
    Furie, Barbara
  - Furth, Jacob, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Furth, John J., 1966-1967 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Kaufman, Herbert E.
  - Gaffron, Hans, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Galanakis, Dennis, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Galston, Arthur W., 1980-1991 (Box 8)
  - Galvin, John, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Gambino, Ray, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Gefter, Malcolm, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Gehrke, Charles, 1976-1977, n.d. (Box 8)
    Kuo, Kenneth W.
  - Geiduschek, E.P., 1969 (Box 8)
  - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Genetics Society of America, 1968 (Box 8)
  - George, Philip, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Georgetown University, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Gerner, Edward W., 1969 (Box 8)
  - Gest, Howard, 1963, 1974, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Ghuysen, Jean-Marie, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Gibson, Wade, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Ginoza, William, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Ginsberg, Ann Meredith, 1973, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Ginsberg, Harold Samuel, 1964-1982 (Box 8)
  - Gjerset, Ruth Anne, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
    -See also Ser.I, Parello, Joseph
  - Glaser, Don, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Glass, H. Bentley, 1977, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Glazer, Robert I., 1980 (Box 8)
    Busch, Harris
  - Glazko, Anthony J., 1975 (Box 8)
  - Glick, Mary Catherine, 1962-1981 (Box 8)
  - Goddard, David R., 1970-1972 (Box 8)
  - Gold, A., 1970 (Box 8)
  - Goldberg, Leon I., 1979 (Box 8)
  - Goldfarb, David, 1969-1986, n.d. (Box 8)
    Polglazov, Boris
  - Goldblum, Natan, 1961-1984 (Box 8)
  - Goldman, Robert P., n.d. (Box 8)
  - Goldwasser, R.A., 1961-1962 (Box 8)
  - Gomatos, Peter, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Goodman, Leon, 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Gopalan, H.N.B., 1972 (Box 8)
  - Goreau, Thomas, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Gordan, Eileen, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Goren, Raphael, 1981-1984 (Box 8)
  - Gorini, Luigi, 1948-1976 (Box 8)
  - Gottlieb, David, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Gotts, J.S., 1955-1956 (Box 8)
  - Graham, Angus F., 1951-1969 (Box 8)
  - Graham, Linda, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Granick, Sam, 1963 (Box 8)
  - Green, David E., 1962 (Box 8)
  - Green, Maurice (Box 8)
    Mudd, Stuart
    -See also Ser.I, Cline, Richard E.
    -See also Ser.I, Miller, Gail L.
    -See also Ser.I, Westphal, O.
    - Folder #1, 1954-1976 (Box 8)
    - Folder #2, 1977-1985 (Box 8)
  - Greenberg, Charles S., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Greenberg, Michael L., 1979-1985 (Box 8)
    Plant Physiology
  - Greenblatt, Charles L., 1978-1981 (Box 8)
  - Greer, Sheldon B., 1989 (Box 8)
  - Griffin, A. Clark, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Grisolia, Santiago, 1962, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Grollman, Arthur P., 1974-1983 (Box 9)
  - Gros, François, 1953 (Box 9)
    in French
  - Gross, J.D., 1972 (Box 9)
  - Gross, Neal, 1972 (Box 9)
  - Grossowicz, Nathan, 1953-1969 (Box 9)
  - Grunberg-Manago, Marianne, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Grundfest, Harry, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Guarino, Linda Ann, 1976-1981 (Box 9)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1947, 1949, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Gumport, Richard, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Gunsalus, Irwin C., 1986 (Box 9)
  - Guschlbauer, Wilhelm, 1964-1981, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Guthrie, Robert, 1956 (Box 9)
  - György, Paul, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Haddox, Mari K., 1980, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Hadley, Henry G., 1973 (Box 9)
  - Hall, Ross, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
  - Hall, Thomas C., 1975 (Box 9)
  - Hallowell, Christopher, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Halpern, Salmon R., 1971 (Box 9)
  - Halvorson, Harlyn, 1987, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Hampton, Alexander, 1968, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Hanawalt, Philip C., 1958 (Box 9)
  - Hancock, R.L., 1987 (Box 9)
  - Handler, Philip, 1968-1981 (Box 9)
  - Haney, Anne, 1972 (Box 9)
  - Harden, Victoria A., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Harold, Franklin M., 1957 (Box 9)
  - Harrison, Arthur P., Jr., 1963-1965 (Box 9)
  - Hartman, Philip E., 1962-1965, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Hartwell, Jonathan L., 1974 (Box 9)
  - Haskins, Caryl P., 1988 (Box 9)
    Bitonti, Alan J.
    -See also Ser.I, Bitonti, Alan J.
  - Hastings, J. Woodland, 1969, 1984 (Box 9)
  - The Hastings Center, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Hattman, Stanley, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Hauschka, Theodore S., 1971 (Box 9)
  - Haverford College, 1955, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Hayashi, S., 1986 (Box 9)
  - Hayashi, Teru, 1962-1983 (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.I, Illinois Institute of Technology
  - The Health Effects Institute, 1981 (Box 9)
  - The Hebrew University, 1970-1983 (Box 9)
    Altman, Arie; Greenblatt, Charles L.; Keynan, Alex
  - Hecht, Sidney, 1978-1983 (Box 9)
  - Hedén, C.-G. (Box 9)
  - Hegedüs, Alexander, 1956-1957 (Box 9)
  - Hegeman, George D., 1966 (Box 9)
  - Heidelberger, Charles, 1962-1982 (Box 9)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Hendler, Sheldon S., 1973, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Henle, Werner, 1962, 1982, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Heppel, Leon A., 1965-1974, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Herbst, Edward J., 1969, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Herriott, Roger M., 1956-1984 (Box 9)
  - Herrmann, Ernest C., Jr., 1972-1979 (Box 9)
  - Hershey, Alfred D., 1952-1972; 30.0 Item(s) (Box 9)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Conferences and symposia; Publication; Requests for reprints; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Hershfield, Michael S., 1983, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Hiatt, Howard H., 1960-1962 (Box 9)
  - Hill, James M., 1976-1979 (Box 9)
  - Hirst, G.K., 1957 (Box 9)
  - Hitchings, George H., 1981, 1988, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Ho, Dah Hsi Wang, 1975-1976, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Hoberman, Henry, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Hoffman-Berling, H., 1969 (Box 9)
  - Hoffmann-La Roche and Company, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Hoffner, Nancy, [196-] (Box 9)
  - Hofmann, Klaus, 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Hollaender, Alexander, 1955, 1972; 2.0 Item(s) (Box 9)
    Conferences and symposia; Oak Ridge National Laboratory; Radiation genetics; Requests for reprints
  - Holland, James F., 1974 (Box 9)
  - Holland, John, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Holleb, Arthur, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Höltje, Joachim-Volker, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Holtzer, Howard, 1968, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Horecker, Bernard L., 1949-1956 (Box 9)
  - Horowitz, Norman H., 1962, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 9)
    -See also Ser.I, Tamm, Igor
  - Horwitz, Jerome P., 1966-1974 (Box 9)
  - Hosakawa, Keiichi, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Hotchkiss, Rollin, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Howard University, 1964-1965 (Box 9)
  - Hruby, Dennis E., 1976 (Box 10)
  - Hubert-Habart, Michel, 1960-1984 (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.I, Latarjet, Raymond
  - Huebner, Robert J., 1971 (Box 10)
  - Hurwitz, Charles, 1966-1970 (Box 10)
  - Hurwitz, Jerard, 1968-1983 (Box 10)
  - Hutchinson, Franklin, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Hutner, Seymour H., 1976-1981 (Box 10)
  - I, Josephine, 1974, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Ilan, Joseph, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology, 1967 (Box 10)
    Hayashi, Teru
  - Indiana University, 1962-1975 (Box 10)
  - Ingham, Kenneth C., 1990 (Box 10)
  - Ingoglia, Nicholas, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Inouye, Masayori, 1976, 1983, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Institut de Biologie Physico-Chimique, 1961-1963, 1974 (Box 10)
    Some in French
  - Institut Jacques Monod, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Institut Pasteur, 1952-1966 (Box 10)
    Some in French; Jacob, François; Latarjet, Raymond
  - Institute for Medical Research, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Institute for Scientific Information, 1978, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Instituto de Quimica, 1958-1959 (Box 10)
  - Interciencia, 1980-1981, 1986 (Box 10)
  - International Conference on Polyamines, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    Seiler, Nikolaus
  - International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences, 1976 (Box 10)
  - International Congress for Virology, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - International Congress of Biochemistry, 1962 (Box 10)
  - International Congress of Biology, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - International Congress of Microbiology, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - International Chemical and Nuclear Corporation, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - International Journal of Applied Radiation and Isotopes, 1965 (Box 10)
  - International Symposium on Biochemical Basis of Drug Action, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
  - International Union of Biochemistry, 1961-1963 (Box 10)
    Calvin, Melvin; Hedén, C.-G.; Florkin, Marcel; Lederberg, Joshua; Ochoa, Severo
  - Isbell, Horace S., 1951-1958 (Box 10)
  - Isom, Harriet C., 1978 (Box 10)
  - The Israel Cancer Research Fund, 1977-1985 (Box 10)
  - Isselbacher, Kurt J., 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Istituto di Chimica Biologica, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Izumori, Ken, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Jacob, François, 1959-1971, n.d. (Box 10)
    -See also Ser.I, Collège de France
    -See also Ser.I, Institut Pasteur
  - Jacobson, Ann, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Jakubowski, Hieronym, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Jannasch, Holger, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Jansen, Annamarie, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Jaques, Louis B., 1979 (Box 10)
  - Järnefelt, Johan, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Jawetz, Ernest, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Jesaitis, Margeris, 1954 (Box 10)
  - The Johns Hopkins University, 1973-1980 (Box 10)
  - Johnston, Michael, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Joklik, W.K., 1984 (Box 10)
  - Jones, Mary Ellen, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Jones, Terence R., 1984 (Box 10)
  - Jorpes, J. Erik, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Journal of Bacteriology, 1963-1978 (Box 10)
  - The Journal of Biological Chemistry, 1948-1976, n.d. (Box 10)
    Sakai, Ted Tetsuo
    -See also Ser.I, Sakai, Ted Tetsuo
  - Journal of Cell Biology, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Journal of Cellular Physiology, 1965-1976, n.d. (Box 11)
  - The Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1946-1950 (Box 11)
  - The Journal of Immunology, 1950 (Box 11)
  - Journal of Molecular Biology, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    Kendrew, John C.
  - Journal of Virology, 1971-1978 (Box 11)
    North, Thomas W.
  - Jukes, Thomas H., 1968 (Box 11)
  - Kabat, Elvin A., 1944-1985 (Box 11)
  - Kahane, Chaim, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Kaji, Akira, 1968-1972 (Box 11)
  - Kaji, Hideko, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Kalckar, Herman M., 1957, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Kallenbach, Neville R., 1971 (Box 11)
  - Kalman, Thomas I., 1971-1978 (Box 11)
  - Kamen, Martin, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Kanazir, Dusan (Box 11)
    -See also Ser.I, Serbian Academy of Sciences and Arts
    - Folder #1, 1955-1962 (Box 11)
    - Folder #2, 1963-1990, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Kang, Soo-Sang, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Kansas State University, 1972 (Box 11)
    Buck, Clayton A.
  - Kaohsiung Medical College, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Kaper, J.M., 1972-1976, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Kaplan, Ann, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Kaplan, Henry S., 1964, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Kaplan, Nathan, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Kargon, Robert H., 1982 (Box 11)
  - Karkas, John D., 1974 (Box 11)
  - Karnovsky, Manfred L., 1974 (Box 11)
  - Katsh, Seymour, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Katz, Joseph, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Katz, Sidney A., 1970 (Box 11)
  - Katzenellenbogen, John A., 1983 (Box 11)
  - Kaufman, Herbert E., 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    Furth, John J.
  - Kaufman, Seymour, 1958, 1965, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Kaufmann, Elisheva, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Kavenoff, Ruth, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Alvin M., 1965, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Kean, Edward L., 1961 (Box 11)
  - Kearns, David R., 1976 (Box 11)
  - Kellenberger, Eduard, 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Kendrew, John C. (Box 11)
    -See Ser.I, Journal of Molecular Biology
  - Kennedy, Eugene P., 1963 (Box 11)
  - Kennedy, John, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Kennell, David E., 1969 (Box 11)
  - Kerr, Sylvia J., 1972, 1978, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Kersten, Helga (Box 11)
    -See Ser.I, Kersten, Walter
  - Kersten, Walter, 1978-1979, n.d. (Box 11)
    Kersten, Helga
  - Kety, Seymour S., 1963 (Box 11)
  - Keynan, Alex, 1962-1983 (Box 11)
  - Khouvine, Yvonne, 1959-1983 (Box 11)
  - Khym, Joseph X., 1952 (Box 11)
  - Kiefer, Paul A., 1970 (Box 11)
  - Kimball, A.P., 1967 (Box 11)
    -See also Ser.I, Furth, John J.
  - King, C.G., 1952 (Box 11)
  - King, Donald West, 1963-1975 (Box 11)
  - Kirsch, Wolff, 1974, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Kit, Saul, 1957, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Klein, George, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Kleinschmidt, Albrecht K., 1964 (Box 12)
  - Klenow, Hans, 1962-1965 (Box 12)
  - Kluyver, A.J., 1952 (Box 12)
  - Knight, B.C.J.G., 1954, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Knight, Claude Arthur, 1954, 1960-1961, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Koch, Arthur L., 1952, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Koerner, James F., 1960 (Box 12)
  - Kohiyama, Masamichi, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Koop, C. Everett, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - Korant, Bruce D., 1980-1981, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Kornberg, Arthur, 1957-1972 (Box 12)
  - Kornberg, Hans L., 1968-1978 (Box 12)
  - Kovalev, Sergei, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Kozinski, Andrzej W., 1963-1976 (Box 12)
  - Kozloff, Lloyd M., 1951-1985 (Box 12)
  - Krakoff, Irwin H., 1981 (Box 12)
  - Krant, Rita, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Krantz, Allen, 1981 (Box 12)
    -See also Ser.I, Syntex
  - Krebs, Hans A., 1963-1969 (Box 12)
  - Kremzner, Leon T., 1981 (Box 12)
  - Krieg, David R., 1956 (Box 12)
  - Krikorian, A.D., 1980 (Box 12)
  - Krim, Mathilde, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Krisch, Henry M., 1969 (Box 12)
  - Krishnaswamy, P.R., 1980 (Box 12)
  - Kruger, Detlev, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Kufe, Donald W., 1986 (Box 12)
  - Kun, Ernest, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Kunitz, Moses, 1951, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Kunkel, L.O., 1954 (Box 12)
  - Kunz, Bernard A., 1988 (Box 12)
  - Kupke, D.W., 1979 (Box 12)
  - Laboratorio Internazionale di Genetica e Biofisica, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Lala, Anil K., 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 12)
  - The Lalor Foundation, 1950-1965 (Box 12)
  - Landman, Otto E., 1958 (Box 12)
  - Lapi, Lillie ("Toni"), 1971-1976 (Box 12)
  - Lark, Gordan, 1964 (Box 12)
  - Albert and Mary Lasker Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Latarjet, Raymond, 1948-1973, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Lauffer, Max A., 1944-1984 (Box 12)
    -See also Ser.I, Advances in Virus Research
  - Leboy, Phoebe S., 1969-1976 (Box 12)
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1956-1984; 19.0 Item(s) (Box 12)
    Avery, Oswald Theodore; Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Genetics Society of America -- Golden Jubilee; History of biology, especially genetics; Molecular genetics; Recommendations; Requests for reprints
  - Lederberg, Seymour, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Lederer, Edgar, 1965-1982 (Box 12)
  - Lederle Laboratories, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Leopold, A. Carl, 1980 (Box 12)
  - LePage, G.A., 1946 (Box 12)
  - Lerman, Leonard, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Leskowitz, Sidney, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Leung, Hazel Barner, 1957-1983 (Box 12)
    The American Museum of Natural History; Moscona, A.A.
    -See also Ser.I, The American Museum of Natural History
    -See also Ser.I, Moscona, A.A.; Levin, Eugene G.
    -See Ser.I, Clark, Jeffrey L.
  - Levin, Morton L., 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Levin, Robert, 1973, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Levine, Lawrence, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Levine, Rachmiel, 1981-1984 (Box 12)
  - Levinthal, Cyrus, 1956, 1958, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Levintow, Leon, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Levy, Carl, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Lewin, Ralph A., 1964-1965, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Lewontin, Richard C., 1971 (Box 12)
  - Lichtenstein, Janet (Box 12)
    -See Ser.I, Stern, Janet Lichtenstein
  - Life Sciences, 1979 (Box 12)
  - The Lilly Research Laboratories, 1951, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Lim, Ramon (Box 13)
    - Folder #1, 1965-1975 (Box 13)
    - Folder #2, 1976-1985 (Box 13)
  - Lim, Victoria, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Lipmann, Fritz, 1966, 1975, 1981, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Littauer, Uri, 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Littleton, Cecily D., 1953 (Box 13)
  - Lockhart, W.R., 1965 (Box 13)
  - Loeb, Marilyn R., 1965-1983 (Box 13)
  - Loewenstein, Werner R., 1978 (Box 13)
  - Loftfield, Robert B., 1979-1982 (Box 13)
  - London, Irving M., 1971 (Box 13)
  - Long, Perrin H., 1950 (Box 13)
  - Lorand, Laszlo, 1972-1984 (Box 13)
  - Lowe, Peter A., 1981 (Box 13)
  - Lowry, Oliver H., 1945 (Box 13)
  - Lubin, Martin, 1965, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Lubochinsky, Bernard, 1965, 1968, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Lucas-Lenard, Jean, 1964-1980 (Box 13)
    -See also Ser.I, Roth, Jay S.
  - Ludwig, George D., 1966, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Luk, Gordon D., 1989 (Box 13)
  - Luria, Salvador E., 1947-1969, 1984; 24.0 Item(s) (Box 13)
    -See also Ser.I, American Society for Microbiology